clubpenguingang.com 2010-06-23

# Privacy Policy

This is the Website of Mimo & 3130 Studio. Or sites covered by this policy are: Mimo.cc, Clubpenguingang.com, Clubpenguindscheats.com, MimoGames.com.

 **Information Collected**

We respect the privacy of children, and do not collect any more personal information than reasonably necessary to enable them to participate in the activities we offer at our Websites.

With respect to our online information collection practices from children under 13 years of age:

Please note that parents may consent to the above collection and use without necessarily consenting to the disclosure of personal information to third parties.

With respect to the collection by other organizations of personal information from children at our site, our policy is:  
We do not have any agreements with outside organizations to collect personal information at our site.

 **Use and Sharing of Information**

The ONLY information we collect from children is email addresses used to post comments on mimo.cc.

With respect to sharing information:  
we do not share children’s email addresses with anyone other than those who provide support for the internal operations of the Website and our agents (e.g., contractors who provide fulfillment services or technical support to the Website).

We have received the following commitments for security of information from third parties with whom we share personal information

All third parties with whom we share information have agreed to maintain security and integrity of personal information

 **Parental Review**

Parents can review the information that we have collected from their children online, prevent the further use or maintenance of such information, or direct the deletion of their children’s personal information by:

  * emailing us at info(at)mimo.cc
